Have you ever eaten kosher food?
你吃过洁食吗？
That's food which conforms to the Jewish dietary regulations of kashrut.
洁食指的是符合犹太饮食教规“卡舒特”的食物。
These regulations forbid consuming pork or shellfish of any kind, for example.
比如这类教规禁止食用猪肉和任何贝类海鲜。
Meat from other animals, such as cows and lamb, are okay provided restrictions are met. But they must be slaughtered according to set guidelines.
其他动物的肉类，比如牛肉和羊肉，只要满足相关限制条件就是允许食用的，但这些动物必须按照既定准则宰杀。
All kosher rulings are overseen by trained rabbis from a kosher certification agency. They inspect, uphold and grant rights to label a food kosher.
所有洁食相关的规定都由洁食认证机构的专业拉比监督执行，他们负责检查、监督并授予食品标注洁食标识的权利。
Ordinarily, kosher food is associated with the Jewish faith, but it's becoming very popular among non-Jews too.
通常来说，洁食都与犹太教信仰挂钩，但如今它在非犹太人中也变得十分受欢迎。
According to the Jewish telegraphic agency, as of 2018 there were approximately 7.5 million Jews in the United States.
据犹太电讯社的数据显示，截至2018年，美国约有750万犹太人。
But, according to a study by the Quartz business news website, 41% of all packaged foodstuffs there are certified kosher.
但根据商业新闻网站《石英》的一项研究，美国市场上41%的包装食品都获得了洁食认证。
In fact, the global kosher food market is predicted to rise to $60 billion in annual sales by 2025 - according to PR Newswire, a press release distribution network.
而据新闻稿发布机构美通社预测，到2025年，全球洁食市场的年销售额预计将达到600亿美元。
Why might this be?
出现这种情况的原因是什么呢？
One reason is the possible perception that kosher food is cleaner or healthier.
其一，人们可能认为洁食更干净、更健康。
Another is the guarantee that certain allergens, such as shellfish, will definitely not be permitted.
其二，洁食能保证绝对不含某些过敏原，比如贝类海鲜。
And its protocols mean anyone seeking to avoid certain ingredients like gelatine, can do so.
此外，洁食的生产流程规定，也能让那些想要避开明胶等特定成分的人放心食用。
“It appeals to a more health-conscious consumer,” says Menachem Lubinsky, CEO of Lubicom.
卢比康公司首席执行官梅纳赫姆·卢宾斯基表示：“洁食对那些更注重健康的消费者很有吸引力。”
They're the organiser of "Kosherfest", a two-day event that advertises itself as 'the world's largest and most attended kosher-certified products trade show'.
该公司是“洁食博览会”的主办方，这场为期两天的展会自称是“全球规模最大、参展人数最多的洁食认证产品贸易展”。
In 2019, at its 31st event in New Jersey, attendance was up from the previous year by 800, and 300 new products were on display.
2019年，这场展会在新泽西州举办了第31届，参展人数较前一年增加了800人，现场展示了300种新品。
In addition, non-Jewish-owned companies from places such as Pakistan, South Korea and Italy were in attendance.
此外，来自巴基斯坦、韩国、意大利等地的非犹太裔企业也参与了展会。
So keep your eyes peeled for an authorised kosher trademark the next time you're food shopping.
所以下次采购食品的时候，不妨留意一下官方认证的洁食标识。
Based on their popularity to date, it might not be long before we're all eating a little something kosher.
从洁食当下的受欢迎程度来看，要不了多久，我们每个人或许都会吃上一些洁食。